http://ncseweb.org/privacy-policy-and-disclaimer

Privacy Policy and Disclaimer | National Center for Science Education
Our Partners
Need a Speaker?
Washington Post
"The 1918 flu is still with us": The deadliest pandemic ever is still causing problems today
Our Partners
Need a Speaker?
Privacy Policy
NCSE is committed to respecting the privacy of members, supporters and donors. Our privacy policy has been established to ensure donors that their information will not be shared with any third party.
Information Collected. The types of donor information collected and maintained are:
contact information: name, affiliation (if any), address, phone number, email address;
payment information: last 4 digits of credit card number and expiration date, and billing information;
shipping information: name, complete address;
information concerning how the donor heard about NCSE;
information the donor wishes to share: questions, comments, suggestions; and
donor requests for periodic updates: e.g., we maintain information on donors’ requests to receive NCSE newsletters or periodic mailings related to specific fund-raising appeals.
Sharing of Personal Information. Use of donor information will be limited to the internal purposes of NCSE and only to further the activities and purposes of NCSE with the following three exceptions:
NCSE periodically acknowledges donors by name and by broad range of donation amount (e.g., between $100 and $1000; over $1000) in our newsletter.
NCSE sometimes identifies donors by name, describing them as members of NCSE, in articles on our website and in our newsletter that concern those donors.
NCSE sometimes exchanges the names and addresses of donors with like-minded non-profit organizations. We never rent or exchange telephone numbers or e-mail addresses.
We will honor individual requests not to use donor information in any and all of these ways.
Removing a Donor Name from the NCSE Mailing List. NCSE does not want to send unwanted mail to our donors. Donors should contact us if they wish to be removed from the mailing list.
Contacting Us. Any comments or questions about our donor privacy policy can be emailed to info@ncse.com or you may call us at (510) 601-7203.
Disclaimer
Membership in the National Center for Science Education
NCSE is a membership based 501(c)(3) nonprofit corporation devoted to promoting and enhancing the teaching of science, especially the evolutionary sciences and the climate sciences, in formal and informal education, especially in K-12 public schools.
Membership in the National Center for Science Education includes:
One year's subscription to Reports of the National Center for Science Education (4 issues)
Participation in NCSE's diverse efforts to promote and defend the integrity of science education
Annual memberships are fully tax deductible. A member may cancel membership at any time.
NCSE values the privacy of its members.
NCSE periodically shares members' names and addresses with nonprofit organizations that have similar goals and with selected commercial entities that offer benefits to NCSE members. NCSE will honor requests not to share members' names and addresses with such organizations.
NCSE will honor requests to opt out from receiving mailings from NCSE.
Contacting NCSE
The National Center for Science Education can be contacted:
By postal mail at 1904 Franklin St Suite 600, Oakland CA 94702
By telephone at 510-601-7203
By fax at 510-788-7971
By e-mail at info@ncse.com
Sales
The sale of books listed on the NCSE web site is handled by Amazon.com and Powells.com. NCSE has no direct involvement or responsibility for such sales. However, NCSE receives a small commission on sales that are initiated by using the links provided on the NCSE web site.
On-Line Financial Transactions with NCSE
On-line credit card transactions with NCSE for memberships, donations, or purchases of NCSE merchandise are done using secure technologies and encryption. NCSE makes no use of personal financial data apart from the purpose for which such data are furnished to NCSE, and NCSE strives to protect such data from loss, misuse, disclosure, or unauthorized access.
Revised September 2019
X
Making the Grade?
Learn More
1904 Franklin Street, Suite 600
Oakland, CA 94612
510-601-7203
Fax: 510-788-7971
info@ncse.ngo
membership@ncse.ngo
Facebook
Job Opportunities
Science education is constantly evolving!
Want to keep up?
Subscribe to our newsletter for the latest news, events, and resources from NCSE.
National Center for Science Education (NCSE) is a 501(c)(3) tax-exempt organization, EIN 11-2656357. NCSE is supported by individuals, foundations, and scientific societies. Review our annual audited financial statements and IRS 990 forms at GuideStar.
© Copyright 2020 National Center for Science Education.
Privacy Policy and Disclaimer | Disclosures Required by State Law
